[
    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Who founded the World Wide Web Consortium?",
        "answer": "Tim Berners-Lee"
    },

    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Type of programming language used to combine existing components together.",
        "answer": "Scripting Language"
    },

    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Most widely used client-side scripting language and is also used in server-side scripting.",
        "answer": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Conceptualized JavaScript in 1995",
        "answer": "Brendan Eich" 
    },
    {
        "type": "identification",
        "question": "Downloads script asynchronously with HTML and other web resources.",
        "answer": "async"
    },

    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "1xx status codes are:",
        "options": [
            "Informational",
            "Successful",
            "Redirection",
            "Client-side Errors",
            "Server-side Errors"
        ],
        "answer": "Informational"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "2xx status codes are:",
        "options": [
            "Informational",
            "Successful",
            "Redirection",
            "Client-side Errors",
            "Server-side Errors"
        ],
        "answer": "Successful"
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple-choice",
        "question": "3xx status codes are:",
        "options": [
            "Informational",
            "Successful",
            "Redirection",
            "Client-side Errors",
            "Server-side Errors"
        ],
        "answer": "Redirection"
    },
        {
            "type": "multiple-choice",
            "question": "4xx status codes are:",
            "options": [
                "Informational",
                "Successful",
                "Redirection",
                "Client-side Errors",
                "Server-side Errors"
            ],
            "answer": "Client-side Errors"
        },
        {
            "type": "multiple-choice",
            "question": "5xx status codes are:",
            "options": [
                "Successful",
                "Redirection",
                "Informational",
                "Client-side Errors",
                "Server-side Errors"
            ],
            "answer": "Server-side Errors"
        },
        
        
        {
            "type": "multiple-choice",
            "question": "What port does HTTP use?",
            "options": [
                "80",
                "443",
                "8080",
                "1010"
            ],
            "answer": "80"
        },
        
        {
            "type": "multiple-choice",
            "question": "What port does HTTPS use?",
            "options": [
                "80",
                "443",
                "8080",
                "1010"
            ],
            "answer": "443"
        },

        {
            "type": "multiple-choice",
            "question": "What is the URL of the first website?",
            "options": [
                "Myvirtuallearning.org",
                "Google.com",
                "Facebook.com",
                "Info.cern.ch"
            ],
            "answer": "Info.cern.ch"
        },

        {
            "type": "true-or-false",
            "question": "Tim Berners Lee founded the World Wide Web Consortium",
            "answer": "True"
        },

        {
            "type": "true-or-false",
            "question": "id, class, and title are global attributes.",
            "answer": "True"
        },
        {
            "type": "true-or-false",
            "question": "HTML was developed by Tim Berners-Lee at CERN.",
            "answer": "True"
        },

        {
            "type": "true-or-false",
            "question": "CSS is the language used to specify the presentation aspects of structurally marked-up documents.",
            "answer": "True"
        },

        {
            "type": "true-or-false",
            "question": "The CONNECT method establishes a tunnel to the server.",
            "answer": "True"
        },

        {
            "type": "true-or-false",
            "question": "The OPTIONS method describes the communication options for the target resource.",
            "answer": "True"
        },

        {
            "type": "true-or-false",
            "question": "A payload is a resource included in the HTTP response of the server.",
            "answer": "True"
        }

]